Vivek KumarFeatured Resume

(Immediate Joiner) Sr. Software Developer seeking assignment in Software Development, Application Programming, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Gap Analysis, Asp.net core, Mvc, Linq, EF, Sql Server, C#, Jquery, Dot net, C#, LINQ, HTML, Ajax

Current Designation: Sr. Software Developer

Current Company: Chetu

Current Location: Noida

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR, Noida, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [Information Technology]

Key Skills: Sr. Software Developer,Software Development,Application Programming,Program Management,Software Engineering,Project Management,Requirement Gathering,System Analysis,Gap Analysis,Asp.net core,Mvc,Linq,EF,Sql Server,C#,Jquery,Dot net,C#,LINQ,HTML,Ajax

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

ID: 405e95ab50f4878852Last Active: 15-Sep-20Last Modified: 15-Sep-20

Jump to SectionWork Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Summary

(Immediate Joiner) Sr. Software Developer with 5 years of work exposure in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Gap Analysis, Asp.net core, Mvc, Linq, EF, Sql Server, C#, Jquery, Dot net, C#, LINQ, HTML, Ajax.

Currently I am working in dotnet core application with MVC and i have used multi repository pattern inside project.

Roles & Responsibilities:

Worked on architecture, designing and development.

Currently I'm working on Hospital management project and I have implemented architecture of given poject.

Work Experience

Chetu as Sr. Software Developer

Sep 2017 to Till Date

dotnet core developer

Computax as Software Developer

Jan 2017 to May 2017

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from rajasthan technical university in 2014

PG: MBA/PGDM (Information Technology) from Sikkim Manipal University (SMU) in 2017

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

Asp.net core, Mvc5, Linq, EF

SQL Server, C#, jQuery

DOT NET

MS Server, VS, Photoshop

RPA, Automation anywhere

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language Proficiency Read Write Speak

English

Hindi

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Hospital management

Client: US

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Project Details: Dotnet core with MVC APPLICATION